<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><templates><template autoinsert="true" context="org.python.pydev.editor.templates.python" deleted="false" description="Adds a GeoBC docstring 'class' template for you to fill in" enabled="true" name="docclass">${document_class}${cursor}</template><template autoinsert="true" context="org.python.pydev.editor.templates.python" deleted="false" description="Adds a GeoBC docstring 'function' template for you to fill in" enabled="true" name="docfunc">${space_if_py2}</template><template autoinsert="true" context="org.python.pydev.editor.templates.python" deleted="false" description="Adds a GeoBC docstring 'history' template, you need to copy the contents of this entry into your module docstring" enabled="true" name="dochist">'''&#13;
**History:**&#13;
-------------------&#13;
&#13;
:Author: &lt;who made the changes&gt;&#13;
:Modification:&#13;
   - Describe here the changes that were made in bullet form.  Use&#13;
     a new dash charachter '-' to create a new entry!&#13;
:Date: &lt;enter the date the changes were made&gt;&#13;
'''</template><template autoinsert="true" context="org.python.pydev.editor.templates.python" deleted="false" description="Adds a GeoBC docstring 'method' template for you to fill in" enabled="true" name="docmeth">${current_method_args}${cursor}</template><template autoinsert="true" context="org.python.pydev.editor.templates.python" deleted="false" description="Adds a GeoBC docstring 'module' template for you to fill in" enabled="true" name="docmod">"""&#13;
.. &#13;
   OVERVIEW / INFO COMMENTS - DELETE THIS &#13;
   This is a template that can be edited to create&#13;
   documentation that can be used by your script.  The&#13;
   documentation standard that is being used is called&#13;
   reSTructuredText or reST for short.&#13;
   &#13;
   reST can be consumed by a number of different documentation&#13;
   systems including sphinx and epydoc.  Unless you would like&#13;
   to there is no requirement to use these systems.  There &#13;
   is a requirement however to use this script documentation &#13;
   template!&#13;
   &#13;
   As a quick FYI the '..' preceding and following this &#13;
   paragraph are reST comments.  This text can be deleted.&#13;
   &#13;
   This comment and any other text that is surrounded by&#13;
   '..' will not show up in derived documentation   ..&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
About&#13;
=========&#13;
:synopsis:     Quick and Dirty summary of why this module exists&#13;
:moduleauthor: Author here, Can repeat this line with a different author if there was more than one author!&#13;
:date:         Enter Date Here!&#13;
:description:  This is a longer description of what this module does&#13;
               why you wrote it, how it makes the world a better place!&#13;
   &#13;
:comment:  You can enter comments in anywhere!  this is just and &#13;
           example of how you can enter them!&#13;
&#13;
.. COMMAND LINE ARGS COMMENTS - DELETE&#13;
    Is this a script you can run or is it a library simply containing f&#13;
    functionality for other modules.  If its intended to run, then describe&#13;
    how this can be done, but describing args that need to be sent to the &#13;
    script&#13;
    &#13;
    Also fill in the example so that it shows an example of what &#13;
    your script would look like if it were to be run from the command &#13;
    line.&#13;
    &#13;
    If your script is simply a library then you can delete the section &#13;
    below.&#13;
..&#13;
&#13;
Command Line Arguements:&#13;
-------------------&#13;
&#13;
.. cmdoption::  &lt;Fire Perimeter&gt; &#13;
&#13;
      Fire perimeter from FIMT Schema (Feature Class)&#13;
    &#13;
.. cmdoption::  &lt;Fire to Export&gt; &#13;
&#13;
      List of fires to export (The fire number in the feature class above that you want to load)&#13;
      &#13;
Example to run on the command line::&#13;
&#13;
    WFMB_FireP_export_v5.py \\mirage\Geomatics$$\current_fire_season\PrinceGeorge\G9\G90522\G90522_20120929_1_p.shp G90522&#13;
    &#13;
..  NOTES COMMENT&#13;
    if at any point you wish to include a note in your documentation the following &#13;
    section shows how you can do that! syntax below shows how&#13;
..&#13;
&#13;
.. note:: &#13;
&#13;
      This is an example of a note&#13;
&#13;
.. Does your script create any outputs.  If so describe those outputs &#13;
   here.&#13;
..&#13;
&#13;
Outputs:&#13;
-------------------&#13;
If you script creates any outputs delete this line here and replace it &#13;
with a description of the outputs produced by your script.  If your script&#13;
does not produce any outputs delete the entire output section!&#13;
&#13;
Dependencies:&#13;
-------------------&#13;
Does your script have any dependencies?  If it does then include them here.  Only&#13;
include dependencies like 3rd party modules that your script requires that are not &#13;
part of arcgis or that are not part of a standard GTS python install.&#13;
&#13;
..  --- HISTORY ----&#13;
    The following sections document changes that are made to your &#13;
    script.  After the inital version is created if there are changes&#13;
    made or fixes docuemnt what was done or functionality that was added.&#13;
    &#13;
    you can also create a new history entry using the template:&#13;
    dochist&#13;
..&#13;
      &#13;
**History:**&#13;
-------------------&#13;
&#13;
:Author: &lt;who made the changes&gt;&#13;
:Modification:&#13;
   - Describe here the changes that were made in bullet form.  Use&#13;
     a new dash charachter '-' to create a new entry!&#13;
:Date: &lt;enter the date the changes were made&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
API DOC:&#13;
===============     &#13;
"""</template></templates>